well it was the first weekend of the NFL
season which explains why you're all
still hung over and your dad's yelling
at you in honor of football's return
tonight's hashtag is NFL rappers
examples might be Fat Joe Montana or
Tupac
conversion or Dr Dre will treat your
concussion
now he's not a real doctor I don't know
put 60 Seconds clock I go yes Jay will I
am pleading no contest okay
points yes Randy uh Lil Drew Breezy okay
points yes Jay uh Marky Mark Sanchez and
the Funky Bunch okay great points
Brandon the Tennessee tians nice
ohandy a red zones Thugs and Harmony
okay all right
F Jay Little John foot
ball no they're on the fence I'll allow
it f it just made it yeah Randy just hit
the upright and bounced in just bounced
in came in uh how about em and EMT Smith
okay good yeah I like it Bron L Cool J
Cutler ah good points he's got a bad
knee J Young Drew Breezy oh oh Twisted
it makes you think yes yes Brandon uh
NFL w hey
oh